https://littlehouseontheprairie.com/privacy-policy/

Search
This privacy policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information.  Please read this policy carefully.
We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our sites.  We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone.  Please refer back to this policy regularly.
We do not collect any individually identifiable information about you through the Site.  We have access to such information only if you choose to share with us either directly or by e-mail.  We do not and will not sell information about users of the Site to third parties.  Nor do we share such information except as described below.
In certain instances, we may contract with nonaffiliated companies to perform services for us. Where necessary, we will disclose information we have about you to these third parties.  In all such cases, we provide the third party with only the information necessary to carry out its assigned responsibilities and only for that purpose.  And, we require these third parties to treat your private information with the same degree of confidentiality that we do.  In addition, we will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are compelled by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances, such as an attempted breach of the security of the Site, or a physical or property threat to you or others.  We may also transfer user information, including any personally identifiable information you have provided to us, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of related assets or corporate division or other fundamental corporate change.
Friendly Family Productions, LLC (“FFP”) may track IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to keep track of a user’s session, while the user’s personal information remains totally anonymous. Tracking IP addresses can give us important information about our visitors.  For example, we can learn which parts of the Site users are visiting and how long they stay.  When FFP receives information about you or about your session, we may use it for research or to improve the Site and the services we offer you.  In addition to using such information to administer the Site and, in the aggregate, to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on the Site, we may share this aggregate statistical information with our partners, suppliers and other third parties, but we will not share any individual names, personal navigational or other personal information.
Privacy of Children
We understand that young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize that they may not understand all the provisions of our policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices that are made available to our adult users.  We strongly urge all parents to participate in their children’s exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online.  We may, at our discretion, require users under 18 to obtain the consent of a parent or guardian to view certain content, and we may limit access to certain content to users above a specified age.  You agree to abide by any such restrictions, and not to help anyone avoid these restrictions.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.
